This is a work of fiction. Any resemblance to anyone, living or dead, is coincidental.
Sydney Davis.
I would start thechief k
dean.
TeaSzah.
Somebody save me.
Let your warm hands break right through me.
Don't care how you do it.
Just stay, stay.
Come on.
I've been waiting for you.
I've made this whole world shine for you.
Just stay, stay.
Come on.
Hope you guys are hungry because there are plenty more where these came from.
Loach, you really didn't have to do all this.
At least let me help.
I should make some eggs.
Oh, no, no, Mrs. Kent.
You can just sit down and relax.
Look, here I am using your home as my own personal Motel 6.
It's really the least I can do.
Yeah, well, I'm not that hungry, so I'm gonna have some OJ.
Come on.
Breakfast is the most important meal of the day.
Bacon?
Okay, so I'm never gonna make it to the Cordon Bleu,
but I thought it would be less of a disaster than helping out on the farm.
Huh.
Maybe ironing.
Lois, what's going on?
What do you mean?
You made us breakfast.
You're offering to do chores.
You want something.
No.
It's called being nice.
Yeah, well, if you were any nicer, we'd starve.
Clark.
He's right, Mrs. Kent.
Look...
Um...
See, you guys have been so good to me already.
It's kind of hard to ask for yet another favor, so...
But, um...
Hello?
Anybody home?
Oh, sweetie, what's your name?
Hi.
I'm so happy to see you.
Um, meet my sister, Lucy.
Uh, she was kinda hoping maybe she could crash here for a couple days.
I know it's last minute, but I had this school break, and I'm willing to sleep in the barn.
No, that's okay. Lois can sleep in the barn.
Nobody has to sleep out there.
We'd love to have you, Lucy.
Um, you can stay in Lois' room.
Look, we'll, uh, we'll go up and get your things set up.
Okay.
So, Lucy, Lois has told us absolutely nothing about you.
There's not much to tell.
Oh, please, let me gloat.
She is getting straight A's at one of the most prestigious prep schools in Europe,
she is fluent in three languages,
and she is fending off Ivy League colleges with a stick.
Wow, that's impressive.
What happened to Lois?
You're gonna find that Clark's charm is an acquired taste,
much like his sense of fashion.
Well, thanks for letting me stay.
I don't know how I'm going to repay you.
Well, just tell me plenty of embarrassing stories about Lois.
Funny guy.
Well, I'm just gonna go wash four time zones worth of airport connections.
Lucy?
Are you sure everything's okay?
Now that I'm here with you, it's perfect.
You know, you cheated on that last stretch, young lady.
I had you beat.
Well, I only offered you a kiss, didn't think you'd actually fall for it.
Oh, my God.
Hold on.
Is anything missing?
I don't know.
My jewelry's still here.
My wallet's right where I left it.
Okay, well, if nothing valuable's missing, then...
The stone.
I'm sorry.
Well, now that I've finally found the stone...
Who else could've known it was here?
I don't know.
Well, no one saw me take it in China.
Maybe, uh, maybe lexer Lionel figured it out.
Or Clark.
I mean, he always said there was a side of him that you never really knew.
I don't care who did this, Jason.
I don't care about these stones.
This isn't some bad dream that you can just blink away.
This is real life.
We have to find that stone.
No, we don't.
Jason, our relationship has become more
about chasing artifacts than it is about you and me.
And that isn't our relationship.
Remember when our biggest problem was
trying to find a place to steal a kiss?
Yeah, I usually prefer it under the bleachers.
Well, there is no reason why we can't go back to those days
without worrying about break-ins and artifacts
and the Luthers.
And Clark End.
You're right.
Then whoever took the stone,
they can just keep it.
And we'll just concentrate on the only thing that really matters.
Us.
Hope you're thirsty.
What are you doing?
I figured I would help out and get the morning milk.
I spent last night drinking.
I'm sorry.
I was just having a spring break on my friend's farm in the Swiss countryside.
Well, you know, you didn't really have to do that.
I figured if I'm gonna stay,
I have to pull my own weight.
Hey, Lois. Did you hear that?
I'm sorry. Did you say something?
Go get changed. I'm going to work.
Since when did you work?
Since today. I'm helping your mom out at the Talon.
So Chloe is going to be your official Smallville tour guide.
Not that there's much to say.
Not that there's much to see.
No, I don't know.
So far it looks pretty good.
Hmm.
I don't know.
Don't let all that flirting go to your head.
She goes to an all-girls school.
You're probably the first guy she's talked to in a couple months.
Lois, I don't want you to get the wrong idea,
but ever since Lucy came to town, you've been grumpier than normal.
Are you not happy to see your sister?
Of course I am.
Look, there's a thing with sisters.
You can love them without really liking them.
You don't like your own sister.
More like she's not very crazy about me.
Not that I blame her.
Ew.
Look, you might be a little rough around the edges.
As far as sisters go, Lucy could do a lot worse.
Uh, thanks for the ringing endorsement.
When my mother died, my dad had two girls he didn't know how to deal with.
So he did what every good military leader would do.
He instituted a chain of command, and I reported to him...
Lucy reported to you?
Yeah.
Take sibling rivalry to a whole new level.
I had to make sure she had three square meals,
got to school, did her homework.
You became her mother.
Yeah, except I was...
not prepared.
I used to give her advice like, uh,
you know, don't kiss a boy or you're gonna get pregnant.
And yeah, maybe she had a few more chores than most kids.
Is that why she decided to go to my mother's?
Yeah.
Why?
Well, at her boarding school?
Uh, uh, unlike your family, there was no discussion.
You know, when the general gives an order, you're expected to carry it out.
Well, it sounds kinda harsh.
Trust me.
Lucy got the better end of the deal.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
She totally deserves it.
But I guess there was just a part of me that was always jealous she got out and I didn't.
I gotta go to work.
I hear your mother's a slave driver.
I need a half-calf soy latte, no foam, no whip,
and a blueberry muffin top, hold the stem.
Whatever happened to regular old black coffee?
Two lanes under one roof. That's gotta be interesting.
I haven't had a hot shower in two days,
and the laundry machine is running nonstop.
The phone line is consistently busy.
No, it's nice having them around.
It kind of takes a loneliness out of the house.
Yeah, I always hated the sound of a quiet home.
Whoa, is that Lois with a tray? Hey, Kaz.
Yes, it is. It's kind of like a free floor show.
Have you two been catching up?
Um, yeah, Lucy's just filling me in on all her hidden talents.
She was a violinist for the Zurich Youth Orchestra.
It was nothing. It's just a hobby.
Given their reputation in Europe,
I highly doubt it.
I doubt that.
Oh, sorry, Lucy, this is...
Lex Luthor.
I read your profile in Fortune magazine a couple months ago.
I thought your theories on the future of American business
were very interesting.
Oh, I'd be curious to hear what you think of my piano skills.
Drop by the mansion. I'd love to play with a serious musician.
Ugh! Ah, crap!
Oh!
I'm gonna go help her out.
Lucy, who's that guy staring at you back there?
I don't know.
Lisa, are you going to be all right?
I'm really sorry.
It was me.
Maybe Lisa liked being with Darla.
I should go chat to you in the sense of Ж 2014.
Now, again, I'll know what to do tomorrow.
Rose and Lisa are looking for me.
Lily, I told you.
You did.
You spent three days in that apartment.
Listen, I've been talking to groups of people allorta.
Now I have to specialize in one.
You gave me that map because you knew I'd end up in China
And you knew I'd find that stone
It was all one big calculated ploy, wasn't it?
If I had the foresight which you attribute to me
I wouldn't need any ancient artifacts to help me
If you've got any kind of foresight
You will let me know where that stone is right now
Otherwise this is going to get very ugly
So now in addition to hurling accusations
You decide to threaten me?
You break into her apartment
You go through her private things
I assure you breaking and entering is not my style
Your lost treasure isn't here, Mr. Teague
You'll have to look somewhere else
Good day
I'm not going anywhere, Luther
Until you give me that stone
And you convince me that you didn't take it
You storm in here
You accuse me of some ham-fisted home invasion
Why are you doing this?
This is a crime
Is it an act?
An elaborate diversion?
Don't turn this around on me!
I think we both know there's nothing stronger
Than the love between mother and son
And I'm sure Miss Lang agrees
This is code at least
The longer I keep this up
The easier it gets
Until the end
So put me down
Look around
When you're working
I can't lose hope
No matter what
I'm the type of person
Who's not все the more
For you
I can go to secret
Then I'll get Héctor
I'll peach your preference
One stick
The level that's at the top
Of your 서 Cerberus
I'm sorry.
I mistake, bud.
Excuse me, officer.
I appreciate your need to fill your speeding ticket quota,
but could we make this quick?
Put your hands over your head.
What?
Put your hands up now.
Look, I think there's been a mistake.
I may have been speeding.
Go get some bonds, Mr. Futhura.
Oh, my God.
No, no, no, just stay calm, okay?
Nice try.
Dump it in the bag.
Thank you.
Good night.
You wouldn't want Lucy to be an only child, would you?
You wouldn't want Lucy to be an only child.
Take my word for it, there's no cash on the premises.
Wait, where's Marcus Becker?
Never heard of him.
I don't know.
Fox!
Clark, he's got the girls.
Hey! Somebody!
It's no use.
You're totally and utterly screwed.
Oh, let's not jump to conclusions here.
I have a history of getting us out of the jams you get us into.
I'll think of something.
Lois, this isn't like us getting ourselves locked in the mess hall pantry
or getting lost on our bikes in Bangkok.
I don't get it. You got your money.
Why don't you go back home, eat some Swiss cheese,
and live happily ever after? You don't need us.
But I do. The Luthor Well has only just been tapped.
I'm here to strike it rich.
You son of a bitch. You're holding us for ransom?
Lucy, zip it.
Let my sister go.
You don't need both of us.
Sure I do.
A pair of lanes, it definitely ups the ante.
The world would be a whole lot worse without her in it than without me, all right?
She's the one with the future.
If she'd only learned to behave herself.
Eat up, girls.
How generous of you. I thought you'd let us starve.
One with a sticker has no tomatoes.
Lucy?
Yeah?
How did he know you don't like tomatoes?
Lucy Lane has been conning us this whole time.
That's a pretty bold accusation, Clark.
The drop-off was a fake. There was no warehouse.
And Lucy was the only one who knew about the GPS.
I mean, how else would Becker have known to treat the briefcase like the plague?
Becker's a pro. He could simply be cautious about the money.
It's all part of a bigger plan.
The way she accidentally woke me up on her way to steal from the talent.
She knew I'd catch her in the act.
Her sob story about not being able to fit in at school.
It was all a set-up.
In order to win my sympathy, so I'd come to you for the money.
She played us like a Stradivarius.
What I don't understand is why abduct Lois?
I know it's a con, but why kidnap your own sister?
Well, they say sibling rivalries run deep.
Line one, Mr. Luther. It's Becker.
Lex Luther.
Place $500,000 in bearer bonds.
I tracked a trailer on Highway 54 just north of Cherry Hill.
That's not how it works.
Clark?
I swear, Lois, it wasn't supposed to end up this way.
When Michael Hoover was throwing dirt cloths at you, who kicked his butt, huh?
Who was the one who let you sleep in her bed and listen to you snore every night after Mom died?
Lois, I'm sorry.
Well, sorry's not good enough.
I want to know why.
I want to know why you turned to a life of crime.
Why did you turn to a life of crime when you have everything in the world going for you?
You're as close to frickin' perfect as it gets.
Because that's what the General always wanted.
And I just went along and played the part.
From the day I left for school, all I wanted was to go home.
Why didn't you tell the General that?
How could I?
It was clear he didn't want me around.
He wanted you.
What are you talking about?
Why do you think he sent me off to school after Mom died?
He sent you off to school because you were brilliant and you deserved the best education available.
Well, you can think whatever you want.
But the fact is, I always envied you.
Me?
I was being dragged around the world like a spare piece of luggage.
Yeah, but you had something I never had.
What?
You had Dad.
Luce, I don't think either of us ever had Dad.
I'm sorry I got you into this, Lois.
Don't worry about it.
We've been in far worse trouble than this.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, I can't let this go on hasn't.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Come on.
We're pulling over. Now!
How you feeling?
Well, I have a newfound appreciation for seat belts, I can tell you that.
What are you gonna do with my sister?
I don't know.
I don't have a choice. I have to notify the authorities.
Hey! Hey!
Lucy!
Lex! Any luck finding Lucy?
No. All that turned up was the car minus my $50,000.
Look, Lex, I know that Lois feels really badly about this, but there's really no way she's gonna be...
Clark, I'm not here to collect.
Besides, having Becker in custody is worth a lot more to me than 50 grand.
You deal. In Zurich.
Well, I'm glad that someone came out of this ahead.
So how's Lois?
Um, I don't know. She hasn't said anything all day.
But I don't know why Lucy would run away. I mean, Lois is her family.
Just because you have the same blood running through your veins doesn't make you family.
Look at us, Clark.
I'm a product of my father's breeding.
He needed an heir.
But your parents chose you out of love.
I take your family any day of the week.
I just think Lois and Lucy could have been closer.
Hopefully one day they will be.
But that's up to them.
So quit blaming yourself for what happened.
Lex.
Did you ever miss not having a sibling?
I used to.
Until I met you, Clark.
You're closer to me than any blood brother.
You have great secrets.
Hey.
Have you recovered from Hurricane Lucy yet?
I just hope she changes her ways before she gets herself hurt.
You know it never fails. Keeping secrets always leads to trouble.
I don't know which is more difficult.
being the one keeping the secret or the one who's being duped?
Have you talked to Lois?
She's been holed up in her room all day.
She took it all pretty hard.
Well, ever since I can remember,
the one thing Lois has always wanted
is to protect her little sister.
I guess no matter how bad you want to,
you just can't save everyone.
But it doesn't stop you from trying, does it, Clark?
Dad, clearly the idea of personal space is lost on you.
Lex, one of your employees paid me a visit recently,
and I wasn't clear whether it was official business
or what it was.
As far as I know, our outstanding business is finished.
Well, he, Jason T., that's who it was,
accused me of taking something that, uh,
didn't belong to me, of stealing.
Well, it wouldn't be the first time.
Be that as it may.
The accusation was false.
But given what's missing,
I almost wish I was guilty.
What was it?
You know the answer to that question, Lex.
You're the one who took it from him.
Dad, if you want to play games,
there's a deck of cards in the parlor.
Lex, let's talk about games.
You hire someone to travel to China
to search for an ancient artifact.
He finds it, he steals it,
but he keeps it for himself.
Then you have to steal it back from him.
You've turned hot potato into an art form, son.
Jason Teague found the stone?
Either you are the best con man in the world,
or you are truly, unbelievably naive.
Good afternoon, Lex.
The telescopes were for geeks and stalkers.
Yeah, well, as was proven over the last few days,
I can seriously misjudge people.
You know, if you've come to kick me off the farm,
I completely understand.
Yeah, um, actually, I came here to tell you
we have food in the oven, if you're hungry.
Thanks.
How you holding up?
I just got off the phone with the general.
Oh, that was all the screaming I heard from the house.
Yeah.
Well, apparently, he is.
Very disappointed in me for letting this happen,
and as far as my family chain of command goes,
I am the weakest link.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
You know, there's something cathartic
about telling a three-star general to go to hell.
Uh, you know, all these years, I thought I had my sister pegged,
but, uh, in reality, she's a complete stranger to me.
Even if that were true, I think that if she called you tomorrow,
you'd be there in a second to help her.
Yeah, I would.
She's my sister.
I don't think Lucy's all that bad.
You're amazing, Smallville.
You always look for the best in people,
even when they walk all over you.
I guess that explains why we're friends.
Oh, we're friends now?
What?
I won't tell anyone if you don't.
No, that's written in the wind
Take you to higher ground
Come on, don't look down
Cause I'm showing you where to begin
Better everything
Now it all begins
You've got to feel it
You've got to fly
Fly
Fly Fly
Run
Out
아니라
Run